usimmigrationsupport.org 2008-05-13

# US Immigration Support - Privacy Policy

|  | Immigration Guides  
---  
| **U.S. Citizenship:**  
---  
 •  | [US Citizenship Application](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/citizenship_application.html)  
 •  | [US Citizenship Package](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/citizenship_package.html)  
 •  | [US Citizenship Test](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/citizenship_test.html)  
 •  | [Dual Citizenship](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/dual_citizenship.html)  
 •  | [Certificate of Citizenship](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/citizenship_certificate.html)  
 •  | [Certificate of Naturalization](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/certificate_naturalization.html)  
**Green Cards:**  
 •  | [Green Card Application](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/greencard.html)  
 •  | [Green Card Information](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/green_cards.html)  
 •  | [Green Card Renewal](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/greencard_renewal.html)  
 •  | [Green Card Replacement](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/greencard_replacement.html)  
 •  | [Green Card Adoption](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/greencard_adoption.html)  
 •  | [Green Card Change/Update](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/greencard_update.html)  
 •  | [Green Card Employment](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/greencard_employment.html)  
 •  | [Green Card Investment](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/greencard_investment.html)  
 •  | [Green Card Marriage](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/greencard_marriage.html)  
 •  | [Green Card Lottery](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/greencardlottery.html)  
 •  | [Green Card Relatives](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/greencard_relatives.html)  
 •  | [Change of Address](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/addresschange.html)  
 •  | [Medical Exam](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/medicalexam.html)  
 •  | [Special Immigrants](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/greencard_specialimmigrant.html)  
 •  | [Remove Conditions](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/remove_conditions.html)  
 •  | [Reentry Permit](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/reentry_permit.html)  
**United States Visas:**  
 •  | [B-1 Business Visa](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/visa_b1.html)  
 •  | [B-2 Tourist Visa](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/visa_b2.html)  
 •  | [B-1/B-2 Visa Extension](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/visa_b1b2extension.html)  
 •  | [C-1 Transit Visa](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/visa_c1.html)  
 •  | [E-1 Treaty Trader Visa](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/visa_e1.html)  
 •  | [E-2 Treaty Investor Visa](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/visa_e2.html)  
 •  | [E-3 Visa for Australians](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/visa_e3.html)  
 •  | [F-1 Student Visa](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/visa_f1.html)  
 •  | [H-1B Work Visa](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/visa_h1b.html)  
 •  | [H-2B Work Visa](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/visa_h2b.html)  
 •  | [H-3 Trainee Visa](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/visa_h3.html)  
 •  | [J-1 Exchange Visitor Visa](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/visa_j1.html)  
 •  | [K-1 Fiancee/Fiance Visa](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/visa_k1.html)  
 •  | [L-1 Intracompany Work Visa](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/visa_l1.html)  
 •  | [Nurse Work Visa](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/visa_nurse.html)  
 •  | [O-1 Extraordinary Ability](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/visa_o1.html)  
 •  | [P Visa Athlete/Entertainer](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/visa_p.html)  
 •  | [R-1 Religious Visa](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/visa_r1.html)  
 •  | [TN Nafta Work Visa](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/visa_tn.html)  
 •  | [Visa Waiver Program](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/visa_waiver.html)  
**United States Passport:**  
 •  | [Passport Application](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/passport.html)  
 •  | [Renewals and Updates](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/passport_renewal.html)  
 •  | [Passport Card](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/passportcard.html)  
**Business & Finance:**  
 •  | [Get a U.S. Credit Card](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/creditcard.html)  
 •  | [Start a Business in the U.S.](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/startbusiness.html)  
**Employment:**  
 •  | [Form I-9](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/form_i9_employment_eligibility.html)  
 •  | [Green Card Employment](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/greencard_employment.html)  
 •  | [Get a Job in the U.S.](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/jobs.html)  
 •  | [Internships in the U.S.](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/internships.html)  
**Other Products:**  
 •  | [Asylum and Refugee](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/asylum_refugee.html)  
 •  | [Birth Certificate](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/birth_certificate.html)  
 •  | [Change of Address](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/addresschange.html)  
 •  | [Deportation](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/deportation.html)  
 •  | [FOIA Request](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/foia.html)  
 •  | [Form I-94](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/form_i94.html)  
 •  | [How to Get Married](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/marriage.html)  
 •  | [ITIN Application](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/itin.html)  
 •  | [Social Security Card](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/social_security.html)  
 •  | [U.S. Drivers License](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/drivers_license.html)  
 •  | [U.S. Newcomer's Guide](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/newcomers.html)  
Immigration Forms  
---  
|  •  | [Immigration Forms](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/subscription_forms.php?osCsid=76cc2a8f5419a9baee28b9541f2d8f31)  
---|---  
Resources  
---  
|  •  | [Immigration Amnesty](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/amnesty.html)  
---|---  
 •  | [Immigration Articles](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/immigration_articles.html)  
 •  | [Immigration Guides](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/immigration_guides.html)  
 •  | [Immigration Links](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/resources.html)  
 •  | [Immigration News](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/news.html)  
About us  
---  
|  •  | Home  
---|---  
 •  | Certifications  
 •  | Disclaimer  
 •  | Frequently Asked Questions  
 •  | Contact us  

| 

[ ](http://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.usimmigrationsupport.org&sealid=101)US Publishers, Inc. is a licensee of the TRUSTe Web Privacy Seal Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build user’s trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the Web site [www.usimmigrationsupport.org](http://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/). Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact our legal department (contact information at the bottom of this page). If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at [ http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php) TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.

U.S. Immigration Support (a division of U.S. Publishers Inc, Delaware Corporation) is committed to protecting our clients' privacy. U.S. Immigration Support only uses the information we collect to process orders requested by our clients. As a visitor to our website, you have the right to understand our information privacy practices. We understand that submitting your information over the Internet involves a great deal of trust on your part and we take this trust very seriously. Our highest priority is to ensure the security and confidentiality of our clients' personally identifiable information such as name, address, phone number, email address and credit card details. Please review our disclaimers and terms of conditions for more information.

**What Information We Collect**  
We do not collect any information by you browsing our website. If you choose to order any of our products or services, you must voluntarily provide us with your name, address, phone number, email address and credit card information. Your information is not shared with any person, business or organization. No credit card information is stored on our servers. U.S. Immigration Support uses Authorize.net to process credit card transactions. Authorize.net is a leading provider of payment gateway services making it able for customers to purchase products online. Authorize.net will never use your personal information for any other reason. Visit our Business and Website Certifications section for more information.

**Cookies**  
A third party cookie server places cookies on our website in order to collect and provides us with basic website analytics, such as unique visitors, pages views, entry pages, exit pages, search engine referring information, and other general website information. No Personally Identifiable Information [PII] is collected.

**Your Account**  
In order to receive our free newsletter or to download a product, customers need to voluntarily create an account with U.S. Immigration Support. There is no cost associated with creating an account. You can change all the information in your account including your email at any time by going to the “[My Account](https://www.usimmigrationsupport.org/login.php)” page on our website. If you do not wish to keep your account any longer, please contact us and we will delete your account. Your account page is also the best place to go to opt-out of receiving our newsletter.

**Use of Your Data**  
The information you voluntarily provide to us is only used to process your order. User data is never disclosed to any third parties unless as otherwise disclosed in this privacy statement.

**Security**  
Our shopping cart includes a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) certificate to protect our customers’ information when shopping online. SSL technology encrypts the customers’ name, address, and credit card information between your computer and our server. We work closely with Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover to eliminate any fraudulent transactions. It is easy to see that your connection is secure as the URL of your website will change from http:// to https:// indicating that the connection is secure during the check-out process. Please visit our Website Security and Encryption page for additional information. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Changes in this Privacy Statement**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.   
  
**Contact our Legal Department**  
Our legal department can assist you if you have any questions. Please use the contact information below 

_only for legal questions_ concerning our organization. General questions should be submitted to our customer service department.  |  |  **Legal Department** |  **US Immigration Support**  
511 Avenue of the Americas # 45  
New York, NY 10011  
|  | (646) 792-3296  
---|---  
  
**Last Updated:** February 14, 2008

* * *
